

ALPER AKTAŞ
STUDENT

CONTACT INFO

\ +90 534 621 81 05

≥ aktasalper99@gmail.com

in /aktasalper/

yethranayeh.github.io

Stanbul, Avcılar / Turkey

EDUCATION

Ege University

English Language and Literature **2017 - Present**

Küçükçekmece High School

Foreign Language Class **2015** - **2017**

Çakmaklı Cumhuriyet High School 2013 - 2015

LANGUAGES

Turkish - Native

English - CEFR C1

REFERENCES

Çağrı Babuçcuoğlu

Software Lead, Front-end Team Lead

1Pixel Digital Agency

cagribabuccuoglu@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a 23 year old English Language and Literature student interested in software development. My entry to software development began with taking online courses on Python and building small projects with it, using various libraries. After I worked as a front-end developer intern, I have been mainly working on front-end projects since then.

EXPERIENCES

OCT 2021 - NOV 2021 FRONT-END DEVELOPER INTERN

1PIXEL DIGITAL AGENCY Coding functional and responsive sections of pages that correspond to their respective graphical designs, which were provided as issues in Jira Agile development environment.

Integrating created page sections into Shopify themes to provide customizable and ease to use controls to merchants. In addition to integrating these sections to themes, fetching dynamic store data into page elements using Shopify Liquid templating language.

MAY 2020 - AUG 2021 FREELANCER.COM

FREELANCE VIDEO EDITOR

Editing & creating advertisement, music and presentation videos for clients

SKILLS & FAMILIARITY

FRONTEND

- > React|S
- > Typescript
- > Vite / webpack
- > Alpine.js
- > Bootstrap

> Django

PYTHON

> Selenium

- > PyQt5
- > Matplotlib

DBMS

- > PostgreSQL
- > SQLite
- > MongoDB

CERTIFICATES

React (Basic)
HackerRank

10 Apr, 2022

Advanced

-d - - d - d - d

Bilgi Teknolojileri ve İletişim Kurumu

Python Programming: From Beginner to

2021

Python (Basic Skill Assessment)

HackerRank

16 Jun, 2021

SQL (Basic)

HackerRank

12 Aug, 2021